- Kung Fu!
- Kung Fu?
Yes maybe.
(Shoulder) oh.
(Axel) Aj, aj ... Hörrudu!
There were several of you who wanted to see "Challenge".
- "Challenge".
- Yes!
After all, we have done "Gummy vs. Real Food" on this channel before.
But since we are in Portugal, we have noticed that there are a lot of exciting chip flavors, so today we do ...
Kung Fu!
No, not again.
We make chips vs.
Real food!
- Are you tagged?
- (both) Yes!
- Should we get started?
- Okay!
- (both) Yes!
Chips with ketchup flavor ...
... or ketchup.
Here you go.
- Harry, should we drive "mix"?
- Okay, once.
Okay, should we drive?
1, 2, 3.
Ketchup?
Ketchup chips?
Yes.
There are chips with ketchup flavor, or ketchup.
Okay!
- Do they taste ketchup?
- A little.
Maybe you should dip them in ketchup?
Then they taste a little better.
- Can I taste?
- mm.
They are very good!
Do not force from someone else's plate.
- Okay, next.
- Yes, next.
Chips with taste of air -dried ham, or air -dried ham.
- "Bon Appétit."
(Tasty meal) - I don't want to mix.
No, Harry.
No, I don't want to mix either.
1, 2, 3!
- Ham?
- ham chips?
"What the ..." (what in ...)
(Alma) So ... Oh ...
"Oh my God."
(Oh my God)
Test.
- Smurf.
(Both at the same time) Smurf!
Chips with a taste of pepper, or pepper.
And since there is a little red paprika powder in the picture here, we take some paprika powder on the bell pepper as well.
Here you go.
- No, Harry.
Don't peek.
- No, I smell.
- I want to change.
- I don't want to change.
- Okay.
- 1, 2, 3.
I knew it.
- Paprika?
- With something on.
- What's that?
- something.
Yuk.
What is this?
Pepper with something on.
- No, I eat my own.
- He eats chips.
1, 2, 3.
(Alma screams)
- (Joanna) How are your chips, then?
- They are totally okay.
Isn't that strong?
No.
I think I'll test.
Will probably bull on the tongue.
Have you tested chili before?
Mm.
- Does it hurt?
- No.
- Is it hot?
- No, there is no danger.
- What is the situation, Harry?
- I ate one.
Oh.